Franz Waxman Papers
Franz Waxman Papers
- Recordings
  - Professional recordings
    - Rendezvous with Destiny, 12/29/1940; 10/21/1944; waxman_0718; Shellac disc
      Third Acceptance Speech, Side A; Foreign Policy Speech, Side B
    - Rendezvous with Destiny, 01/06/1941; 10/21/1944; waxman_0719; Shellac disc
      "Lend-Lease" Message to Congress, Side A; Foreign Policy Speech, Side B
    - Rendezvous with Destiny, 01/06/1941; 01/20/1945; waxman_0720; Shellac disc
      "Lend-Lease" Message to Congress, Side A; Fourth Inaugural Address, Side B
    - Rendezvous with Destiny, 05/27/1941; 03/01/1945; waxman_0721; Shellac disc
      Fireside Chat Before Pan-American Union Board, Side A; Report to Congress on the Crimea Conference, Side B
    - Rendezvous with Destiny, 09/11/1941; 04/??/1945; 04/16/1945; waxman_0722; Shellac disc
      Labor Day Broadcast Warning to Axis Vessels, Side A; Jefferson Day Address read by Carleton Smith, Side B; Tribute by President Truman, Side B
    - Requiem, Adagio f. Streicher, waxman_0865; Spelled "Waxmann" on case; Barber piece, "Adagio for Strings"; Aufgenommen in der Meistersinger halle; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
    - Return Peyton Place, waxman_0435; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Theme Demonstration Orchestra, Side A
    - Rhapsody For Orchestra and Saxophone, waxman_0621; Shellac disc
    - Rhapsody In War, waxman_0816; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Outro; KHJ Signoff
    - Rhapsody in Wax, 02/20/1940; waxman_0807; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Closing; KHJ Signoff
    - Roll On, Mississippi, Roll On, waxman_0288; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Roll On, Mississippi, Roll On, Side A; Shout, Sister, Shout!, Side B
    - Romeo and Juliet (Sides 1 and 3 of 4), waxman_0217; Opera; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Romeo and Juliet (Sides 2 and 4 of 4), waxman_0218; Opera; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rosenkavalier, waxman_0360; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Roses From The South, waxman_0599; Shellac disc
      Roses From The South, Side A; Tales From The Vienna Woods, Side B
    - Roumanian Rhapsody #1 in A Major, waxman_0693; orchestral music; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part #1, side A; Part #2, side B
    - Roumanian Rhapsody #1 in A Major, waxman_0692; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Roumanian Rhapsody No. 1 in A Major, waxman_0249; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Ruth, waxman_0903; Ruth TV dub good quality with dialogue.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - 's wird schone Mad'ln geben, waxman_0306; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      's wird schone Mad'ln geben, Side A; Ja, ja der Wein ist gut, Side B
    - Salome's Dance, waxman_0371; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Satan Superstar, 1978; waxman_0745; VinylDisc
      Side One Satan Speaks; Dr Jekyll and Mr. Hyde; Rosemary's Baby; King of Kings; Side Two The Seventh Victim; Exorcist II The Heretic; The Omen
    - Scapino, A Comedy Overture, waxman_0339; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - School for Wives, waxman_0681; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Side Two, Side A; Side Four, Side B
    - School For Wives, waxman_0680; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Side One, Side A; Side Three, Side B
    - The School for Wives, waxman_0992; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 121)
    - The School for Wives, waxman_0993; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 121)
    - Selections of Waxman compositions played and conducted by Franz Waxman, waxman_0902; Typed notes inside package. "All selections are from Original sound track albums or television transmissions (please excuse inferior sound quality on latter) conducted and played by the composer with the exception of Lisa conducted by Victor Young and main theme of Cimarron conducted by David Rose.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
      Prelude and The wishing star fron Taras Bulba; Love them fon a Place in the Sun; Katsumi theme from Sayonara; Lisa fron Rear Window conducted by Victor Young; Main theme from Cimarron conducted by David Young; The Hilltop and Theme from Peyton Place; Rosanna from Adventures of a Young Man; theme from My Geisha; aicha theme from Lost command; Title song form this is my Love, sung by connie Russell; Prelude from the Story of Ruth; End title and song from Beloved Infidel; FDR and Eleanor themes from Sunrise at Campobello.
    - Serenade A La Poupee, waxman_0276; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Serenade A La Poupee, Side A; Capriccio, Side B
    - Serenade in G Major, K. 525, Eine kleine Nachtmusik, Musical Joke, K. 522 = The Village Musicia, Andante, C Major for Flute and Orchestra, K. 315, 3/25/1956; waxman_0996; County Museum Music Program; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 121)
    - Shining Hour, waxman_0798; VinylDisc
      Waltz for 2 Pianos with Orchestral Variations
    - Shining Hour, 11/10/1938; waxman_0797; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Chopin Variations
    - Shostakovich #1, waxman_0767; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Shostakovich #1
    - Si Je Ne T'avais Pas Connu, waxman_0260; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Si Je Ne T'avais Pas Connu, Side A; Jai' Pas Su y Faire, Side B
    - Siegfried Idyll, 02/12/1938; waxman_0047; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Silver Chalice, waxman_0738; VinylDisc
      Side One Main Title; New Father; Little Helena; Basil The Slave; Luke; Simon the Magician; The Sacred Cup; The Chase; Basil Loves Helena; Battle; Deborra's Lament; Finale
    - The Silver Chalice, waxman_0889; Soundtrack Dubbing; Starts on R Channel; Finishes on L Channel; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 144 (Oversize 117)
      The Silver Chalice
    - The Silver Chalice, Basil Loves Helena, Desert Fight, Deborah's Lament, Finale, 11/29/1954; waxman_0968; Reel 2; waxman_0967 is reel 1; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - The Silver Chalice, The New Father, Little Helena, Basil the Slave, Luke, Simon the Magician, The Sacred Cup, The Chase, Deborah is Hurt, 11/29/1954; waxman_0967; Reel 1; waxman_0968 is reel 2; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Sinfojnia for Two Orchestras, waxman_0658; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Sinfojnia for Two Orchestras
    - Sinfonetta for Strings and Timpani, 1978; waxman_0744; VinylDisc
      Side 1 Sinfoniette for Strings and Timpani; Piano Concerto No. 2; Side 2 Piano Concerto No. 2
    - Sinfonia for Two Orchestras; Abraham In Egypt (2 of 2), waxman_1069; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Sinfonia for Two Orchestras; Abraham In Egypt (1 of 2), waxman_1068; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Sinfonietta, Movement 1 Allegro, waxman_0866; Waxman sinfonetta 1st movement allegro; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
    - Sinfonietta for Strings and Timpani, waxman_0827; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - The Song of Bernadette; Anastasia; A Child is Born, waxman_0965; Gift from Charles (?) To John Waxman; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - The Song Of Terezin (1 of 2), waxman_1101; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - The Song Of Terezin (2 of 2), waxman_1102; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Sorcerer's Apprentice; Concerto, 02/12/1938; 02/19/1938; waxman_0048; side B (Concerto) is from Feb 19 performance; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Soundtrack Exerpts, waxman_0887; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Indian Fighter; Sunset Boulevard; Suspicion; Possessed; Botany Bay; Only the Valiant; Elephant Walls; Run Silent Run Deep; Diamond [unreadable]; Celiar Nick Beal; Doris Day Show with Perry Como; [unreadable]; Count Your Blessings
    - South Pacific, waxman_0314; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Dites Moi, Side A; A Cock-Eyes Optimist, Side B
    - South Pacific, waxman_0315; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      There is Nothin' Like A Dame Men's Chorus
    - South Pacific, waxman_0316; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Younger Than Springtime, Side A; Bloody Mary, Side B
    - Special Dreamers, 10/28/1972; waxman_0963; Culturial Affairs # 4; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Special Dreamers; Rebecca, waxman_0869; Culturial Affairs; Standard School Broadcasts; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
    - The Spectacular World of Classic Film Scores: 20 Highlights from the Best-Selling RCA Series, 1978; waxman_0733; Film Soundtrack Compilation; VinylDisc
      Side A Fanfares for Motion Picture Studios 1:27; Star Wars Main Title Williams 5:40; Captain Blood Overture Korngold 2:58; Now Voyger Love Scene and Finale 2:42; Gone With the Wind Polka Steiner 1:05; Elizabeth and Essex Elizabeth's Theme Korngold 1:53; The Caine Mutiny March Steiner 2:33; Citizen Kane Salammbo's Aria Herrmann 4:12; Knights of the Round Table Scherzo Hawks In Flight Rozsa 1:17; Objective Burma! Parachute Drop Waxman 2:16; THe Guns of Navarone Prelude Tiomkin 2:20; Side B Julius Caesar Overture Rosza 4:30; Peyton Place Original Main Title Waxman 3:22; The Thing (From Another World) Suite Tiomkin 10:33; King of the Khyber Rifles the Attack on the Mountain Stronghold Herrmann 3:11; Salome the Dance of the Seven Veile Amfittheatrof 5:02
    - The Spider's Feast; Invitation to Dance; Tarentella, 02/19/1938; waxman_0049; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Spitfire Prelude, waxman_0358; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - St. James Infirmary Blues, waxman_0320; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      St. James Infirmary Blues, Side A; Eastman, Side A; Waterboy, Side B
    - Stand Up and Sing, waxman_0289; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      It's Not You, Side A; There's Always Tomorrow, Side B
    - Standard Symphony, 05/09/1940; waxman_0430; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Rebecca, Side A
    - Stereo Test Record, waxman_0749; Shellac disc
      test record; may not actually be part of Waxman at all?
    - Story of Ruth, Selected Cues, Boaz, Accuration, Boaz and Ruth, Finale, waxman_0828; Selected Cues; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Stravinsky Rehearsal (1 of 2), waxman_1038; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Stravinsky Rehearsal (2 of 2), waxman_1039; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - String Quartet in F, 01/01/1938; waxman_0707; Lacquer discs/acetates
      String Quartet in F, Op. 135, Side A; Tod and Verklarung, Side B
    - Suicide Club (1 of 9), waxman_0515; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Main Title - Part I
    - Suicide Club (2 of 9), waxman_0516; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Prologue - Part I
    - Suicide Club (3 of 9), waxman_0517; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Father & Son
    - Suicide Club (4 of 9), waxman_0519; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The Ambassador
    - Suicide Club (5 of 9), waxman_0520; Lacquer discs/acetates
      [Unreadable]
    - Suicide Club (6 of 9), waxman_0521; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The Hide-Out
    - Suicide Club (7 of 9), waxman_0522; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The Suicide Club
    - Suicide Club (8 of 9), waxman_0518; Lacquer discs/acetates
      On The Boat
    - Suicide Club (9 of 9), waxman_0523; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Prologue - Part II
    - Suite from the Allied Artists Film Crime In The Streets, 1956; waxman_0734; VinylDisc
      Side One Crime In The Streets 1. The Plot; 2. The Crime; 3. The Celebration; Side Two Three Sketches 1. Nostalgia; 2. Song; 3. Blues; Theme Variations & Fugato
    - Suite from the Allied Artists Film Crime In The Streets, 1956; waxman_0735; VinylDisc
    - Suite No. 2 in B minor for Flute and Strings, 5/16/1965; waxman_0834; Gala Orchestral Concert; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Suite No.2, waxman_1081; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Suite, The Path Of Thunder (1 of 2), waxman_1085; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Suite, The Path Of Thunder (2 of 2), waxman_1086; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - The Sunrise Call, waxman_0282; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      The Sunrise Call, Side A; Lover's Wooing, Side A
    - Sunset Boulevard: The Classic Film Scores of Franz Waxman The Bride of Frankenstein - A Place in the Sun - Prince Valiant - Rebecca - The Philadelphia Story - Old Acquaintance - Taras Bulba, 1974; waxman_0753; Film Soundtrack Compilation; VinylDisc
    - Sutter's Gold (1 of 3), waxman_0874; Part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation recordings of acetate discs held in the Belfer Audio Archive. Re-recorded at the Syracuse University Audio Archives 1979. Sutter's Gold sound track (cellutone records 3-5-36) acetate 33 1/3 rpm (1 of 3 reels); 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      side 1 gay Hawaiian song, Stenla Razne (2); side 2 Stenka Razne (cont'd), Soliders song, N.G., Balalaika Romance; side 3 Hawaiian song at fiesta in Monterray; side 4 Farewell song on the Sandwich Islands (2); side 5 Newspaper Montage (2) San Francisco speed (4)
    - Sutter's Gold (1 of 8), 03/05/1936; waxman_0536; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Sutter's Gold (2 of 3), waxman_0875; Part of Franz Waxman Re-recording project 1979. Re-recorded at the Syracuse University Audio Archives 1997. Sutter's Gold Sound track (Cellutone records 3-5-36) acetate disc 33/1/3 (2of 3 reels);; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      side 6 Death Scene- vocal, N.G, N.G.; side 7 the New Country, N.G., Washington 0 Part 1; Side 8 the wheel' repeat cast' the family arrives; side 9 Death scene- vocal (2) N.G., death scene - with violin; side 10 brass band (2), N.G., in Switzerland
    - Sutter's Gold (2 of 8), 03/05/1936; waxman_0537; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Farewell Song, Side A; Hawaiian Song at the Festival in Montery, Side B
    - Sutter's Gold (3 of 3), waxman_0876; Part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation re-recording project of discs held in Belfer Audio Archive. Re-recorded at the Syracuse Univeristy Audio Archives 1979.Frans Waxman re-recording project Sutter's gold sound track Cellutone records 3-5-36 acetate 33 /1/3; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      side 11 Elizabeth leaving (2); side 12 N.G., Sutter alone, Elizabeth (2); side 13 Main Theme (2) N.G., Seven day righe; Side 14 Main Theme; Side 15 California Montage, Diving Overboard; Side 16 Washington - Part 2
    - Sutter's Gold (3 of 8), 03/06/1936; waxman_0538; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Newspaper Montage, Side A; San Fransisco Speeds, Side A; Death, Side B
    - Sutter's Gold (4 of 8), 03/06/1936; waxman_0539; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The New Country, Side A; Washington I. Part, Side A; The Wheel, Side B; Repeat Cast[Some Tracks Unreadable]
    - Sutter's Gold (5 of 8), 03/06/1936; waxman_0540; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Sutter's Gold (6 of 8), 03/06/1936; waxman_0541; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Sutter Alone, Side A; Elisebeth, Side A; Elisabeth Leaving, Side B
    - Sutter's Gold (7 of 8), 03/06/1936; waxman_0542; Lacquer discs/acetates
      California Montage, Side A; Driving Overboard, Side A; Main Title, Side B
    - Sutter's Gold (8 of 8), 03/06/1936; waxman_0543; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Main Title, Side A; Seven Day Ride, Side A; Washington II Part, Side B
    - Symphonic Fantasy, waxman_0489; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphonic Metamorphosis of Themes by Carl Maria von Weber, 6/4/1963; waxman_0950; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Symphonie Fantastique, waxman_0393; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Symphonie Fantastique, Side A; Joyeuse Marche, Side B
    - Symphonie No. 1, 12/25/1937; waxman_0701; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Symphonie No. 1
    - Symphonie No. 1, 12/25/1937; waxman_0702; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphonie No. 1, 12/25/1937; waxman_0703; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphonie No. 2 Adagio, Allegretto and Finale, 02/12/1938; waxman_0046; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphonie No. 6, 01/08/1938; waxman_0710; Shellac disc
      Symphonie No. 6, Side A; Symphonie No. 6, Side B
    - Symphonie No. 6, 01/08/1938; waxman_0711; Shellac disc
    - Symphonie No. 7 in C, 01/01/1938; waxman_0704; Shellac disc
    - Symphonie No. 7 in C, 01/01/1938; waxman_0705; Shellac disc
      Part 3, Second Movement Conclusion, Side A; Part 4,Side B
    - Symphonie No. 7 in C, 01/01/1938; waxman_0706; Shellac disc
      Part 5, Finale, Side A; Part 6, Finale, String Quartet in F, Side B
    - Symphony, waxman_0690; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony #5 (1 of 5), waxman_0817; Waxman rehearsal; orchestral music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony #5 (2 of 5), waxman_0818; Waxman rehearsal; orchestral music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony #5 (3 of 5), waxman_0819; Waxman rehearsal; orchestral music; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 5, side A; Part 6, side B
    - Symphony #5 (4 of 5), waxman_0820; Waxman rehearsal; orchestral music; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 7, side A; Part 8, side B
    - Symphony #5 (5 of 5), waxman_0821; Waxman rehearsal; orchestral music; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 9, side A
    - Symphony #8 (Side 2 of 3), waxman_0212; Orchestra Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony #8 (Sides 1 and 3 of 3), waxman_0211; Orchestra Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony Espagnol, 1944; waxman_0419; Hollywood Bowl; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony Espagnol, 1944; waxman_0420; Hollywood Bowl; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony Espagnole, waxman_0417; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony Espagnole, waxman_0884; Part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation re-recording of audiodisc acetate 78 rpm. Re-recorded by the Syracuse University Audio Archives 1979.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Symphony Espagnole
    - Symphony Espagnole, waxman_0418; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Lalo, Symphony Espagnole
    - Symphony in C Major, No. 41, Jupiter, 6/5/1954; waxman_0979; Los Angeles Music Festival; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Symphony in D Major; Variations on the Theme of Haydn, 02/26/1938; waxman_0054; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 1 (1 of 2), waxman_0777; Disc label and envelope give the Russian spelling of the composer, "Szostakowicz"; Orchestral Music; off the air recording; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 1, side A; Part 3 side B
    - Symphony No. 1 (2 of 2), waxman_0776; Disc label and envelope give the Russian spelling of the composer, "Szostakowicz"; Orchestral Music; off the air recording; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 2, side A; Part 4 side B
    - Symphony No. 1, Movements 2 through 5; Piano Concerto in A Major, Movement 1, Jun 1960; waxman_0947; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Symphony No. 1 Beginning, waxman_1033; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 1 Conclusion, waxman_1034; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 1 in C Major Opus 21, waxman_0755; VinylDisc
      Symphony No. 1 in c Major Opus 21
    - Symphony No. 10, Adagio, 6/2/1958; waxman_0853; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Symphony No. 101, waxman_1025; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 11 in G minor, Opus 103, "The Year 1905," Movement 1 and 2, 6/8/1959; waxman_0846; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Symphony No. 11 in G minor, Opus 103, The Year 1905, Movements 3 and 4, 06/08/1959; waxman_0845; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Symphony No. 2, waxman_1040; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 2, waxman_1032; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 2 (1 of 2), waxman_1058; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 2 (2 of 2), waxman_1059; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 2, part 2, 6/13/1960; waxman_0849; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Symphony No. 2 and No. 4 (1 of 3), 11/4/1939; waxman_0204; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 2 and No. 4 (2 of 3), 11/4/1939; waxman_0203; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 2 and No. 4 (3 of 3), 11/4/1939; waxman_0205; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 2 for String Orchestra, Movement 2, Concerto for Piano, Trumpet and String Orchestra, 6/18/1956; waxman_0980; 10th anniversary performance; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Symphony No. 2 in D Major Opus 73, Mar 1962; waxman_0924; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Symphony No. 2 in D Major Opus 73, Mar 1962; waxman_0925; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Symphony No. 2 in D Major Opus 73, Mar 1962; waxman_0922; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Symphony No. 3, 11/28/1950; waxman_0225; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 3, waxman_0663; Lacquer discs/acetates
      "Toccata", Side A; Toccata, Side B
    - Symphony No. 3, waxman_0664; Lacquer discs/acetates
      "Chorale", Side A; Toccata, Side B
    - Symphony No. 3, waxman_0665; Lacquer discs/acetates
      "Chorale", Side A; "Chorale", Side B
    - Symphony No. 3, waxman_0666; Lacquer discs/acetates
      "Fugue", Side A; "Fugue", Side B
    - Symphony No. 3, waxman_0667; Lacquer discs/acetates
      "Passacaglia", Side A; "Passacaglia", Side B
    - Symphony No. 3 (2 of 4), 10/27/1939; waxman_0207; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 3 (Disc 1 of 4), 10/27/1939; waxman_0206; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 3 (Disc 3 of 4), 10/27/1939; waxman_0208; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 3, Movement 1, 1/16/1952; waxman_0991; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 121)
    - Symphony No. 3, Movment 2 and 3, 1/16/1952; waxman_0990; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Symphony No. 3, Movment 2 and 3, 1/16/1952; waxman_0989; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Symphony No. 3 in D minor part 2, 6/12/1951; waxman_0847; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Symphony No. 3 in Eb (2 of 4), 01/29/1939; waxman_0179; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 3 in Eb; Pictures at an Exhibition (Disc 3 of 4), 01/29/1939; waxman_0180; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 3 West Side Story (1 of 2), waxman_1054; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 3 West Side Story (2 of 2), waxman_1055; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 4, waxman_0488; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 3, Side A; Symphonic Fantasy Part 2, Side B
    - Symphony No. 4 (1 of 2), waxman_1049; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 4 (2 of 2), waxman_1050; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 4 (2 of 4), waxman_0168; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 4 (Disc 1 of 4), waxman_0167; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 4 (Disc 3 of 4), waxman_0169; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 4 (Disc 4 of 4), waxman_0170; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 4 in C minor, Opus 43, Part 1, 6/11/1959; waxman_0844; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Symphony No. 4 in C minor, Opus 43, Part 2, 6/11/1959; waxman_0945; 8:30 pm performance at Royce Hall, UCLA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Symphony No. 4 in D Major, waxman_0404; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Part 7 - Fourth Movement Finale, Side A; Midsummer Night's Dream, Side B
    - Symphony No. 5, waxman_1084; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Symphony No. 5 Op. 50, waxman_0365; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      1st Movement, Part 2: Temp Giusto, Side A; 2nd Movement, concl.: Andante - Allegro, Side B
    - Symphony No. 5 Op. 50, waxman_0366; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      1st Movement Part 5: Adagio, Side A; 2nd Movement, Part 1: Allegro, Side B
    - Symphony No. 5 Op. 50, waxman_0367; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      1st Movement, Part 3: Tempo Giusto, Side A; 2nd Movement, Part 3: Presto, Side B
    - Symphony No. 5 Op. 50, waxman_0368; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      1st Movement, Part 4: Adagio, Side A; 2nd Movement, Part 2: Allegro-Presto, Side B
    - Symphony No. 5 Op. 50, waxman_0369; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      1st Movement, Part 1: Tempo Giusto, Side A; Prelude to 2nd Act "Maskarade", Side B
    - Symphony No. 6 (Disc 2 of 3), 10/29/1938; waxman_0199; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Symphony No. 6 (Disc 1 of 3), 10/29/1938; waxman_0198; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates